<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>posts on Software and Trading</title>
    <link>https://adanjsuarez.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in posts on Software and Trading</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 10:10:38 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adanjsuarez.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://adanjsuarez.github.io/posts/trading/cryptocurrency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 15:12:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adanjsuarez.github.io/posts/trading/cryptocurrency/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: Cryptos came to stay, but what is insane is their valuation. As an example, when Bitcoin reached $1000 for the first time back in the day, I tweeted something like: “$1000? is the people crazy?”
Cryptos came to stay? Cryptos are not an scam like many argue. Let me tell you a bit of technology history that will put this in perspective. Starting back in the 80s, some developers tried to create the first cryptocurrency -that I have constance of- I remember read about in the old computer magazines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I say not to Timed Coding Test</title>
      <link>https://adanjsuarez.github.io/posts/software/whyisaynottotct/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 16:48:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adanjsuarez.github.io/posts/software/whyisaynottotct/</guid>
      <description>For a good explanation and also good post about timed coding test, (TCT) you can check this link
A TCT could check your ability to solve some problems, algorithms most of them, in a timely manner. It could give you some idea of how good you are as problem solving person. But is that enough? or even good measure of how &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; your are?
Solving TCTs could be trained. With a couple of weeks of intensive work, you could do it decently, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t play in favor of the TCTs to discriminate good from bad developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CGO isn&#39;t a beast</title>
      <link>https://adanjsuarez.github.io/posts/software/cgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 15:32:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adanjsuarez.github.io/posts/software/cgo/</guid>
      <description>The formal info about CGO is here. CGO is a Go tool very useful that you could find in many projects but if you read some articles, they say that CGO is dangerous and your should avoid it. Is it that true?
What is CGO in a simple way? Basically is a tool that allows us to write C code with Go syntax. In other words in C inside Go. Okay, simple but&amp;hellip; why do we need it?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
